Congratulations!
恭喜！
You finished your first Nanodegree, in the school of AI.
你已经完成了你在人工智能学院的第一个纳米学位
You're now hopefully feeling confident with Python,
你现在一定可以自信地使用 Python
and some of the available libraries it offers.You know so much about neural networks.
和 Python 提供的一些库了 你对神经网络也有了很深的理解
Finished your first project,
你还完成了属于自己的第一个项目
and created an image classifier.
创建了一个图像分类器
You have done remarkably well.
你做的非常好
It's only been a few years,
人们模仿自己 用深度神经网络
since deep neural networks have been shown to classify images as well as we humans do.
来分类图像 到现在也不过几年
A short while ago, this would have sounded like science fiction.
不久前 这听起来更像科幻小说
Yet, you just did that.
然而 你刚刚就把科幻小说变成了现实
The ride was probably not an easy one. But, you made it.
或许过程并不容易 但你成功走过来了
You're now ready to continue your AI journey,
你现在随时可以继续探索人工智能
and become an expert.
以成为人工智能专家为目标前进
You may feel that this Nanodegree program,
或许你会觉得这个纳米学位
has satisfied your curiosity or that the skills you have acquired,
已经满足了你的好奇心 又或许你觉得在课程里学到的知识
are just enough to meet your goals.
已经足够自己实现目标了
But, if we gave you an appetite for more,
但我们能给予的远不止这些
and you would like to become an AI expert,
如果你想成为人工智能的专家
Udacity and Udacity School of AI,
我们优达学城和优达学城人工智能学院
offer you many different programs to choose from.
还有诸多课程任你挑选
If you want to take it to the next step,
如果你想继续学习
and learn more about Deep Learning,
进一步了解深度学习
the Deep Learning Nanodegree Program,
深度学习纳米学位
will be a great choice.
会是一个不错的选择
We will teach you many topics,
这个课程涉及许多课题
such as recurrent neural networks,
比如递归神经网络
which focus on sequences of data.
该网络主要用于数据序列的处理
They're essentially neural networks with memory.
本质上是拥有记忆的神经网络
One of the projects we will focus on,
课程的重点实战项目之一
is teaching a quadcopter how to fly.
是让四轴飞行器学会飞行
In the Machine Learning Nanodegree program,
在机器学习纳米学位课程中
you'll master skills that are in demand across countless industries.
你将熟练掌握一些在诸多领域都很吃香的技能
You will learn about supervised learning,
你将学习监督学习
unsupervised learning and much more.
和非监督学习等知识
One of the projects,
这门课程中有一个项目
will be to create your own, dog breed classifier.
要求你亲手创建一个犬种分类器
If you want to learn more specific topics,
如果你想学习一些更加具体的知识
we also offer a Computer Vision, Nanodegree program.
可以试试我们的计算机视觉工程师纳米学位
In this nanodegree, you will learn how machines process images and videos,
你将了解机器是如何处理图像和视频的
for applications that include object recognition and localization,
这种技术可用于目标识别与定位
image captioning, scene understanding,
图像标注、场景理解
and tracking of objects in videos.
和视频物体追踪等等
In the Natural Language Processing Nanodegree program,
在自然语言处理工程师纳米学位中
you will learn about machine learning systems,
你将学习机器学习系统
that understand natural language.
该系统能理解自然语言
Like, text extracted from an article or a blog,
比如从文章或博客中提取的文本
machine translation, text summarization and voice user interfaces like Amazon's Alexa.
这类系统还能进行机器翻译和文本摘要 也能用于亚马逊 Alexa 等语音用户界面
Udacity, also offers more Nanodegree programs.
优达学城还有其它纳米学位
If you're interested in how AI is applied to autonomous systems,
如果你好奇人工智能是怎么应用于自动系统的
check out our self-driving engineer program.
可以关注我们的无人驾驶工程师纳米学位
We also offer flying cars and autonomous flight,
此外 我们还提供飞行汽车、自主飞行
robotic software engineer, and many other Nanodegree programs.
机器人开发等诸多领域的纳米学位课程
It has been our honor teaching you.
很荣幸能与你分享知识
We wish you the best of luck,
祝你好运
in your AI journey to success.
祝你在人工智能领域大获成功